100,000 of us coming together can save
humanity not 100,000 of us marching in
the street not a hundred thousand of us
needing to all agree and get along
before we take a step forward but a
hundred thousand people all need to eat
the 7.5 billion people on this planet
all need to eat if a hundred thousand
people put in a dollar we could create
the app that makes sure we're all fed
what stops you from being fed access to
food access to information access to
systems we can create the platform that
makes sure that we use every square inch
of space that we already own to grow
food and distribute it amongst ourselves
so if you have extra you can give it to
your neighbors if you don't know what to
cook for dinner and that's stopping you
as it does me there is people who have
meal plans with the hope already put in
that that mental labor and they can make
it available to everyone the sky's the
limit for what we can do when we work
together but we don't need everybody to
work together a hundred thousand of us
paying $10 a month into a pool that we
then can use to solve actual problems
with technology paying people to code
and to create our platforms our systems
that we've had the conversations about
we've decided what features and benefits
we want in that we voted on the the ones
with the most priority to start the beta
with and then we create the beta we use
it and we continually improve it until
it meets 99% of our of our of 99% of our
members needs needs not means we don't
need somebody else to solve our problems
we need the tools so that we can come
together and solve our problems I'm not
focusing on the food app because it's
hard to get a hundred thousand people
together all at once if I could I would
but what we're focusing on is creating
the platform design for a conversation
social media platform it actually gives
you people to talk to so that we have
connection and community and from that
space a hundred thousand people being on
that talking about mmm I need food
here's what stops me from eating food
natural solutions are going to arise and
as we were part of this conversation we
have is how do we find those solutions
and we together create a funding funding
system that keeps us that empowers us
and gives us the money to actually move
forward with all of these projects we
create the tools to actually move
forward with all these projects how do
we know what needs to get done how do we
break it down how do we distribute that
that works so that we can we can
contribute to it our data our ideas our
labor that is fun and easy and
incremental right who wouldn't give ten
minutes a week to help save humanity
if you require people like we're already
struggling we're all we're barely
keeping our heads above water and we're
working so hard and getting nowhere that
people hear what I'm trying to create
and they're like I don't have anything
to give you do you just need to take a
fraction of that a tiny bit of that time
energy money they are putting towards
like how much is your food bill gone up
a tiny fraction of that you put in $1
towards a global app that helps you
bring down your cost of food would help
you astronomically but we need to create
it in Reverse we need to have the people
on board before we create it so they
trust it when it's created so they can
say what they need in that app so that
they can we can come together and create
the solutions that we need a hundred
thousand of us which is not where we're
going - starting with me one and then
I'm gonna get a few people and a few bar
people we're using existing technology
to host those conversations while we
create the platform table to hold those
conversations but once we have that
platform we can move forward with
solving all of the problems
simultaneously once we have the platform
and a few tools to actually be able to
move forward with projects so that is
today's video 100,000 of us can create
thanks